Guide to the Cornell University Library Academic Assembly records, 1969-2002.
Cornell University Library Academic Assembly records, 1969-2002
- Academic Assembly, April, 5, 1994; tr-7190a; Cassette Tape
- Academic Assembly, May 3, 1994; tr-7193a; Cassette Tape
- Academic Assembly, June 7, 1994; tr-7193a; Cassette Tape
- Academic Assembly, December 6, 1994; tr-7193a; Cassette Tape
- Minutes, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Agendas, Announcements, Programs, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Council of Librarians, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Orientation Committee, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Orientation Handouts, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Steering Committee, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Minutes, Announcements, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- 1996 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Programs, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Reports, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Orientation Committee, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Steering Committee -- Minutes, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Steering Committee, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Minutes, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Orientation Committee, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Steering Committee -- Minutes, Reports, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Steering Committee -- Correspondence, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Minutes, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Orientation Committee, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Steering Committee, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Minutes, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Orientation Committee, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Standing Committee -- Annual Reports, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Steering Committee, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Library Tour Guest Books, 1994-1995; 1999 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Minutes, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Economic Status Committee, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Professional Development Committee, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Steering Committee, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Steering Committee, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Cornell Expanded, Ray Von Dran, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Academic Assembly Anniversary, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Correspondence, April - July 2002 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Correspondence, July 2001- March 2002 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Steering Committee Minutes, July 2001- May 2002 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Academic Assembly Minutes, September 2001- March 2002 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Programs, October 2001- June 2002 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Minutes, Memos, Correspondence, July-August 2002 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Minutes, Memos, Correspondence, August-October 2002 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Meeting Notes, March-August 2003 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Academic Assembly, 2004-2007 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
- Academic Assembly: meeting minutes, 2006-2008 (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
- Academic Assembly: receipts, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Academic Assembly: statements, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Academic Assembly Committees: annual reports, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Committee on the Economic Status of Librarians: report, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Academic Assembly Steering Committee notebook, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- [A. A.] Steering Committee: minutes and correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- AASC appointments to standing committees, 2007-2009 (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
- AASC: Elections, 2008-2010 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- AASC: Budget, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- AASC statements, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- CULAA tapes 1-10, January-October, Undated; TR-17123-17132 (Box 5)
- Reclaiming Scholarly Communication, Ken Fraizer, 2002; DVD-3 (Box 1)